indialeads.com 2017-12-21

# India Leads - Top Free Classified Site | Free Classified Ads In India | India Classifieds | Post Free Ad

### **Privacy Policy & Terms**

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**  
By using our website to you allow us to show your ad/classified/lead/content on our website or on our affiliate websites.  You agree to receive any promotional communication from us via email/sms etc unless you specifically opt out of it by writing us about it at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1663786563746575647f74737b73567f78727f777a737772653875797b). You allow us to share some of the information related to your searches/interest/usage pattern to our affiliates for marketing purpose. We may also share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Liability**  
This website just facilitates to get your property sold and we are not responsible **by any means** for any damages caused to you. It’s all up to you to who to deal with( _or purchase/sell items_ ) and be responsible for your own decisions. You take full responsibility of making sure that the person/party you are dealing with is not fraud. We are not liable for any direct or indirect damages caused to you as a result of you using our services. We are not responsible for any damages caused to you as result of dealing with the scammers.

**Service Warranty**  
We make no promise regarding our services and you agree to use our services “as is” without any warranty condition. We can terminate our services any time without any prior notice to you. We also hold all rights to terminate your account at any point of time if we feel that you are abusing our services.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard websites, this website uses log files. These include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links**  
This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy policy (or privacy statement) of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside advertising networks and companies in order to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons in order to collect data in the ad serving process. These such cookies and/or web beacons are collected by the companies and/or advertising networks, themselves. We do not have any access to this information. We may work with several advertising networks and companies, such as: (google, yahoo etc). If you have any questions, please check their websites for their respective privacy policies.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:  
By e-mail: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
